Guide to the Graphics collection, 1740-1995 MS2379
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Oversize graphics [formerly flat folio graphics], Circa 1807 - 1960; Series 2
  - The Army and Navy buildings of the United States government, Washington., Circa 1881; Series 2; 1 print: relief; image 17 x 35 cm. (Box 67, Folder 8)
    Cataloging notes: From: The Illustrated London news, Oct. 8, 1881, pages 364.; Army and Navy Buildings in Washington, D.C., now the Old Executive Office Building.
    Subjects: Dwight D. Eisenhower Executive Office Building (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Dwight D. Eisenhower Executive Office Building (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00651008; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Inside a treasury vault in Washington drawn by T. de Thulstrup from a photograph by Bell., Circa [1893]; Series 2; 1 print: relief; image 29 x 22 cm (Box 67, Folder 9)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 884 ff
    Cataloging notes: From: Harper's weekly, Vol. XXXVII, numbers 1908, July 15, 1893, pages [661].; Treasury vault in Washington, D.C.; 3 men shown.
    Subjects: United States. Department of the Treasury Pictorial works.; United States. Department of the Treasury. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01853090; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - In the treasury vaults at Washington from photographs by Bell., Circa [1893?]; Series 2; 2 prints (1 sheet); 29 x 41 cm (Box 67, Folder 10)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 885 ff
    Cataloging notes: From: Harper's weekly Vol. XXXVII, numbers 1908, July 15, 1893.; Men in vaults of the U.S. Treasury weighing gold and silver.
  - The evolution of a bank-note: illustrations of the Bureau of Engraving and Printing from photos by Frances B. Johnson., 1889; Series 2; 8 prints (1 sheet): relief; 42 x 30 cm. (Box 67, Folder 11)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 886 ff
    Cataloging notes: From: Frank Leslie's illustrated newspaper, Oct. 26, 1889, pages 217.; Interior and exterior of U.S. Bureau of Printing and Engraving, Washington, D.C.
    Subjects: United States. Bureau of Engraving and Printing Pictorial works.; United States. Bureau of Engraving and Printing. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00539252; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - The United States Treasury: exterior and interior., 1861; Series 2; 10 prints (1 sheet): relief; 28 x 41 cm. (Box 67, Folder 12)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 887 ff
    Cataloging notes: From: Harper's weekly, Oct. 19, 1861, pages 665.; U.S. Treasury Building, in use since 1838, located at 15th and Pennsylvania Ave., N.W., Washington, D.C. Shows exterior and interior views.
  - United States Patent-Office Department, Washington, D.C. photographed by A. Gardner., 1867; Series 2; 1 print: relief; image 18 x 23 cm. (Box 67, Folder 13)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 888 ff
    Cataloging notes: From: Harper's weekly, Feb. 23, 1867, pages 117.; U.S. patent Office in Washington, D.C.; building constructed starting in 1836 at 8th and F Streets, N.W.; now houses the National Portrait Gallery.
    Subjects: United States. Patent Office Pictorial works.; United States. Patent Office. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00534685; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Washington, D.C.: painting the dome of the Capitol from a sketch by a staff artist., 1882; Series 2; 1 print: relief; image 24 x 18 cm. (Box 67, Folder 14)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 889 ff
    Cataloging notes: From: Frank leslie's illustrated newspaper, Dec. 16, 1882, pages 268.; Two men painting the U.S. Capitol dome; a man and a woman on balcony above observe.
  - The National Museum, Washington, where the inauguration ball was held., 1881; Series 2; 1 print: relief; image 17 x 34 cm. (Box 67, Folder 15)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 890 ff
    Cataloging notes: From: Harper's weekly, March 19, 1881, pages 180.; Text describes inauguration of President James Garfield in 1881.; Smithsonian Institution building in Washington, D.C.; groups of people in foreground.
    Subjects: Garfield, James A. (James Abram), 1831-1881 Inauguration.; Garfield, James A. (James Abram), 1831-1881. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00004703; Smithsonian Institution Pictorial works.; Smithsonian Institution. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00532691; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Washington, D.C.: the inauguration of President Cleveland, March 4th: popular ovation to the President at the moment of the administration of the oath of office from a sketch by C. Upham., 1885; Series 2; 1 print: relief; image 51 x 35 cm. (Box 67, Folder 16)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 891 ff
    Cataloging notes: From: Frank Leslie's illustrated newspaper, March 14, 1885, pages 57.; Inauguration of President Grover Cleveland at the Capitol in Washington, D.C.; large crowd of people in foreground.
    Subjects: Cleveland, Grover, 1837-1908 Inauguration Pictorial works.; Cleveland, Grover, 1837-1908. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00009698; United States Capitol (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; United States Capitol (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00631067; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Our new President: general view of the inauguration ceremonies from a sketch by Theo. R. Davis., Circa [1877]; Series 2; 1 print: relief; image 34 x 51 cm. (Box 67, Folder 17)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 892 ff
    Cataloging notes: From: Harper's weekly, March 24, 1877, pages 228-229.; Inauguration ceremonies at the U.S. Capitol in 1877 for President Rutherford B. Hayes; large crowd of people shown.
    Subjects: Hayes, Rutherford B., 1822-1893 Inauguration Pictorial works.; Hayes, Rutherford B., 1822-1893. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01899568; United States Capitol (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; United States Capitol (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00631067; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Inauguration of Mr. Buchanan, as President of the United States at Washington from a photograph by Whitchurch., 1857; Series 2; 1 print: relief; image 19 x 23 cm. (Box 67, Folder 18)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 893 ff
    Cataloging notes: From: The Illustrated London News, supplement, March 28, 1857, pages 295.; Inauguration of President James Buchanan, at the United States Capitol; large crowd shown.
    Subjects: Buchanan, James, 1791-1868 Inauguration Pictorial works.; Buchanan, James, 1791-1868. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00029121; United States Capitol (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; United States Capitol (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00631067; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Washington, D.C.: workmen decorating the interior of the Pension Building, for the inauguration ball from a sketch by C. Upham., 1885; Series 2; 1 print: relief; image 20 x 23 cm. (Box 67, Folder 19)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 894 ff
    Cataloging notes: From Frank Leslie's illustrated newspaper, March 7, 1885, pages 37.; United States Pension Building being decorated for inaugural ball in Washington, D.C. for President Cleveland; large number of men hanging flags and other decorations.
    Subjects: Cleveland, Grove, 1837-1908 Inauguration Pictorial works.; Pension Building (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.
  - Washington, D.C.: the national House of Representatives as it appeared during the recent struggle of the Democrats to prevent legislation by absenting themselves from their seats; Representative Roswell P. Flower tells some of this Democratic colleagues of a "trap" he had set for certain Republicans of the House photo by Bell., 1890; Series 2; 2 prints (1 sheet); 40 x 28 cm. (Box 67, Folder 20)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 895 ff
    Cataloging notes: From: Frank Leslie's illustrated newspaper, Oct. 11, 1890.; Sketch of U.S. House of Representatives; photograph of Rep. Flower with 4 other House Democrats.
    Subjects: Flower, Roswell P. (Roswell Pettibone), 1835-1899 Portraits.; United States. Congress. House Pictorial works.
  - The great war meeting at Washington, District of Columbia, August 6, 1862., Series 2; 1 print: relief; image 29 x 24 cm. (Box 67, Folder 21)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 897 ff
    Cataloging notes: From: Harper's weekly, volume 6, numbers 295 (Aug. 23, 1862), pages [529].; U.S. Capitol, Washington, D.C.; large crowd for meeting about the Civil War.
  - President Cleveland's cabinet from photographs by Bell and Mora., 1885; Series 2; 7 prints (1 sheet): relief; 41 x 28 cm. (Box 67, Folder 22)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 898 ff
    Cataloging notes: From: Frank Leslie's illustrated newspaper, March 14, 1885, pages 60.; Portraits of President Grover Cleveland's cabinet for his first term in office: Daniel Manning, William C. Endicott, William C. Whitney, Thomas F. Bayard, Augustus H. Garland, Lucius Q.C. Lamar, William P. Vilas.
    Subjects: 1885 - 1889 fast; Politics and government fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01919741; United States Politics and government 1885-1889 Pictorial works.; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - The landing of the Japanese Embassy, with the treaty in a box, at the Navy Yard, Washington., 1860; Series 2; 1 print: relief; image 23 x 35 cm. (Box 67, Folder 23)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 899 ff
    Cataloging notes: From: Harper's weekly, May 26, 1860, pages 328.; Crowd scene at Washington Navy Yard, Japanese ambassadorial group arriving.
    Subjects: Washington Navy Yard Pictorial works.; Washington Navy Yard. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00553426; Diplomatic relations. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01907412; Japan Foreign relations United States Pictorial works.; United States Foreign relations Japan Pictorial works.; Japan. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204082; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Corridor of the House of Representatives, Washington: waiting to see their local representative drawn by W.T. Smedley., Circa [1891]; Series 2; 1 print; image 24 x 35 cm. (Box 67, Folder 24)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 900 ff
    Cataloging notes: From: Harper's weekly, supplement, March 14, 1891.; Group of men in the halls of the United States Congress.
  - A cabinet meeting at the White House photographed by Pach., Circa [1879]; Series 2; 1 print: relief; image 35 x 51 cm. (Box 67, Folder 25)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 901 ff
    Cataloging notes: From: Harper's weekly, April 5, 1879, pages 268-269.; Cabinet meeting of President Rutherford B. Hayes, in the office in the White House.
    Subjects: Hayes, Rutherford B., 1822-1893 Portraits.; Hayes, Rutherford B., 1822-1893. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01899568; 1877 - 1881 fast; Politics and government fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01919741; United States Politics and government 1877-1881 Pictorial works.; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874; Portraits. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423831
  - The White House, Washington, D.C. photographed by L.E. Walker. The presidency, Mr. Ferry announcing the result of the count from a sketch by Theo. R. Davis., 1877; Series 2; 2 prints (1 sheet): relief; 35 x 23 cm. (Box 67, Folder 26)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 902 ff
    Cataloging notes: From: Harper's weekly, March 17, 1877, pages 205.; Front of the White House with many carriages; announcement of election of Rutherford B. Hayes.
    Subjects: Hayes, Rutherford B., 1822-1893 Portraits.; Hayes, Rutherford B., 1822-1893. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01899568; White House (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; White House (Washington, D.C.) 1870-1880.; White House (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00631324; 1876 fast; Presidents United States Election 1876 Pictorial works.; Presidents Election. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01075747; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155; Periodical illustrations 1870-1880. gmgpc; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874; Portraits. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423831; Wood engravings 1870-1880. gmgpc
  - Grand cavalry and artillery review at Washington on September 24, 1861., Circa [1861]; Series 2; 1 print: relief; image 22 x 34 cm. (Box 68, Folder 1)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 961 ff
    Cataloging notes: From: Harper's weekly, Oct. 12, 1861, pages 652.; Review of U.S. Army troops near the Capitol in Washington, with many spectators.
    Subjects: United States. Army. Cavalry Pictorial works.; United States. Army. Cavalry. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00564335; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Unveiling the statue of General Thomas at Washington drawn by W.P. Snyder., Circa [1879]; Series 2; 1 print: relief; image 28 x 24 cm. (Box 68, Folder 2)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 962 ff
    Cataloging notes: From: Harper's weekly, Vol. XXIII, numbers 1197, Dec. 6, 1879, pages [949].; Ceremony at Thomas Circle in Washington, D.C., unveiling the statue of General George H. Thomas.
    Subjects: Thomas, George H. (George Henry), 1816-1870 Statues Pictorial works.; Thomas, George H. (George Henry), 1816-1870. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01899294; Statues. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01132151; Thomas Circle (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Washington (D.C.) Thomas Circle. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01323659; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - General Sherman's residence, Washington, D.C. phot. by Bell Brothers., 1869; Series 2; 1 print: relief; image 9 x 12 cm. (Box 68, Folder 3)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 963 ff
    Cataloging notes: From: Harper's weekly, volume XIII, numbers 644, May 1, 1869, pages [273].; Washington home of Gen. William T. Sherman, Union Civil War officer.
    Subjects: Sherman, William T. (William Tecumseh), 1820-1891 Homes and haunts Pictorial works.; Sherman, William T. (William Tecumseh), 1820-1891. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00049712; Homes. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01353235; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - The inauguration of President Garfield: scenes in Washington from sketches by J.O. Davidson., Circa [1881]; Series 2; 5 prints (1 sheet): relief; sheet 41 x 28 cm. (Box 68, Folder 4)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 964 ff
    Cataloging notes: From: Harper's weekly, March 19, 1881, pages 181.; Parades and gatherings for inauguration of President Garfield, 1881.
  - A "powwow" at the White House from a sketch by W.M. Rouzee., 1881; Series 2; 1 print: relief; image 28 x 23 cm. (Box 68, Folder 5)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 965 ff
    Cataloging notes: From: Harper's weekly, Vol. XXV, numbers 1256, Jan. 22, 1881, pages [49].; United States President Rutherford B. Hayes meeting in White House with an assembly of Indians.
    Subjects: Hayes, Rutherford B., 1822-1893 Portraits.; Hayes, Rutherford B., 1822-1893. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01899568; White House (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; White House (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00631324; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874; Portraits. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423831
  - Any thing to get in: you can't play the old Trojan horse game on Uncle Sam by Th. Nast., 1872; Series 2; 1 print: relief; image 29 x 24 cm. (Box 68, Folder 6)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 966 ff
    Cataloging notes: From: Harper's weekly, Vol. XVI, numbers 815, Aug. 10, 1872, pages [617].; Cartoon depicting an attempt to get a modern Trojan horse into a barricaded Washington, D.C.
    Subjects: 1865 - 1877 fast; Politics and government fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01919741; United States Politics and government 1865-1877 Caricatures and cartoons.; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155; Caricatures and cartoons. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423691
  - The trial of Charles Jules Guiteau: a scene in court from a sketch by J.O. Davidson., 1881; Series 2; 1 print: relief; 23 x 37 cm. (Box 68, Folder 7)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 967 ff
    Cataloging notes: From: Harper's weekly, Dec. 3, 1881, pages 804.; Courtroom scene with identification for numerous people; trial of Charles Guiteau, assassin of President Garfield.
  - Incidents of the trial of Charles Jules Guiteau from sketches by J.O. Davidson., 1881; Series 2; 7 prints (1 sheet): relief; sheet 41 x 29 cm. (Box 68, Folder 8)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 968 ff
    Cataloging notes: From: Harper's weekly, Dec. 3, 1881, pages 805.; Attempts on life of Charles Guiteau, assassin of President James Garfield; portraits of prominent figures in the trial.
    Subjects: Garfield, James A. (James Abram), 1831-1881 Assassination Pictorial works.; Guiteau, Charles J. (Charles Julius), 1841-1882. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n50018818; Garfield, James A. (James Abram), 1831-1881. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00004703; Guiteau, Charles J. (Charles Julius), 1841-1882. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01898134; Assassination. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00818962; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Last honors: lying in state in the rotunda of the national capitol from a sketch by Charles Graham., 1881; Series 2; 1 print: relief; image 23 x 35 cm. (Box 68, Folder 9)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 969 ff
    Cataloging notes: From: Harper's weekly, Oct. 1, 1881.; Coffin of President James A. Garfield lying in state in the U.S. Capitol in Washington, D.C.
    Subjects: Garfield, James A. (James Abram), 1831-1881 Assassination Pictorial works.; Garfield, James A. (James Abram), 1831-1881. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00004703; United States Capitol (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; United States Capitol (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00631067; Assassination. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00818962; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - The President's wedding: the crowd outside the White House drawn by Charles Graham., Circa [1886]; Series 2; 1 print: relief; image 19 x 24 cm. (Box 68, Folder 10)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 970 ff
    Cataloging notes: From: Harper's weekly, volume XXX, numbers 1538, June 12, 1886.; Crowd of people outside the White House on the occasion of President Grover Cleveland's marriage.
    Subjects: Cleveland, Grover, 1837-1908 Marriage Pictorial works.; Cleveland, Grover, 1837-1908. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00009698; White House (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; White House (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00631324; Marriage. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01010443; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - The President's wedding: the ladies of the cabinet., Circa [1886]; Series 2; 4 prints (1 sheet): relief; sheet 44 cm. (Box 68, Folder 11)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 971 ff
    Cataloging notes: From: Harper's weekly, June 12, 1886.; Two portraits from photographs by C.M. Bell, Washington.; Portraits of wives of U.S. cabinet officers: Mary Margareta Manning, Ellen Peabody Endicott, Flora Payne Whitney, and Anna Matilda Vilas.
    Subjects: Endicott, Ellen Peabody Portraits.; Manning, Mary Margareta Portraits.; Vilas, Anna Matilda.; Whitney, Flora P. Portraits.
  - The House of Representatives drawn by T. de Thulstrup., Circa [1886]; Series 2; 1 print: relief; image 35 x 52 cm. (Box 68, Folder 12)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 972 ff
    Cataloging notes: From: Harper's weekly, volume XXX, numbers 1518, Jan. 23, 1886.; Floor of the U.S. House of Representatives, showing most members present.
    Subjects: United States. Congress. House Pictorial works. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n79107874; United States. Congress. House. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00536930 http://id.worldcat.org/fast/536930; Legislative bodies United States 1880-1890. lctgm; Periodical illustrations 1880-1890. gmgpc; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874; Wood engravings 1880-1890. gmgpc
  - The United States Senate drawn by T. de Thulstrup., Circa [1886]; Series 2; 1 print: relief; image 35 x 51 cm. (Box 68, Folder 13)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 973 ff
    Cataloging notes: From: Harper's weekly, volume XXX, numbers 1517, Jan. 16, 1886.; Floor of the United States Senate with most members present.
    Subjects: United States. Congress. Senate Pictorial works. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n79022161; United States. Congress. Senate. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00530422 http://id.worldcat.org/fast/530422; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - The new decorations in the White House drawn by Charles Graham., Circa [1883]; Series 2; 5 prints (1 sheet): relief; sheet 41 x 30 cm. (Box 68, Folder 14)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 974 ff
    Cataloging notes: From: Harper's weekly, volume XXVII, numbers 1359, Jan. 6, 1883.; Several public rooms in the White House in Washington, D.C.
    Subjects: White House (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85146483; White House (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00631324; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - The Garfield monument fair, Washington, D.C.: in the Rotunda from a photograph by C.M. Bell., Circa [1882]; Series 2; 1 print: relief; image 18 x 24 cm. (Box 68, Folder 15)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 975 ff
    Cataloging notes: From: Harper's weekly, volume XXVI, numbers 1355, Dec. 9, 1882.; Display of monument honoring President James A. Garfield; large crowd pictured.
    Subjects: Garfield, James A. (James Abram), 1831-1881 Monuments Pictorial works. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n50015182 http://viaf.org/viaf/76703391; Garfield, James A. (James Abram), 1831-1881. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00004703 http://viaf.org/viaf/76703391; United States Capitol (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85141041; United States Capitol (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00631067; Monuments. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01025892; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Accepted design for the new Congressional library drawn by Louis Joutel from the architect's drawings., Circa [1886]; Series 2; 1 print: relief; image 9 x 24 cm. (Box 68, Folder 16)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 976 ff
    Cataloging notes: From: Harpers's weekly, volume XXX, numbers 1531, April 24, 1886.; Library of Congress, Washington, D.C.; Thomas Jefferson Building.
    Subjects: Library of Congress Thomas Jefferson Building (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85076707; Library of Congress Pictorial works. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n78089035; Library of Congress Thomas Jefferson Building (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00631007; Library of Congress. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00528532 http://id.worldcat.org/fast/528532; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - The Supreme Court of the United States, Washington, D.C.: scenes at the reopening of the income-tax cases, Monday, May 6, 1895 drawn by C.S. Reinhart from a sketch by H.G. Dart., Circa [1895]; Series 2; 1 print; image 34 x 47 cm. (Box 68, Folder 17)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 977 ff